[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community
So, the question here is can we improve
现在的问题是
the model using deep features.
我们能否用深度特征来改进我们的模型
Remember we talked about deep features.
记住当我们谈到深度特征的时候
We explored those quite a bit in this deep learning module how deep
我们研究了 在深度学习模块中
features using a technique called transfer learning can be trained on one domain,
通过一种叫做转换学习的方式深度特征 可以用来训练模型
then applied to images in another domain to learn
然后用它来预测图片
something with even a small amount of labeled data.
甚至能在 训练数据仅仅有为数不多的已标签的图片 的情况下
So in this case, let's just take a look at the length of our train data,
在这个例子中 我们来看一下训练数据的维度
just to get a sense of, we have, well we have 2,000 images so
有一个基础的概念 我们一共有2000张图片
this is a pretty small data set.
不是一个很大的数据集
And so, we can go ahead and see, well can we just
然后我们可以进行下一步
20,000 train images using some deep features.
用深度学习2000多个图片中训练模型
So this is the step you take.
这是你的下一步
So we're gonna load deep_learning_model
所以我们要载入深度学习模型
that was pre-trained and so
这是已经编译好的
here you can use graphlab.load_model to load the model.
只要用Graphlab 进行载入就可以了
And have a model that will stream on the image net data.
模型载入的数据是image net 这个数据
It's over here.
在这里
It's called imagenet _model.
叫做imagenet_model
And this model stream of 1.5 million images,
这个模型会传输150万张图片
a thousand different categories, a different data set,
有着1000个标签 是一个完全不同的数据
1.5 million images, it was what we discussed, the AlexNet model.
150万张图片 也是我们之前提到过的AlextNet 模型
It got medium easy access in 2012 ImageNet competition, so
它在ImageNet 比赛中取胜了
I pretrained a model, and then you can use the model to create
我提前训练过这个模型了 你可以用这个模型来
in our image train a new column called
来训练我们的图片 并且添加新的一列
'deep_features'.
叫做deep_feature 深度特征
And in this new column 'deep_features' what we're gonna do
这新的一列就是
is take this deep_learning_model that we just loaded.
我们刚才载入deep_learning_model 所得到的
Deep_learning_model.
这个deep_learning_model
And I'm going to apply a function called extract_features and
我会运用一个叫做 extract_feature 的函数来提取特征
what the extract_features does is extract those deep features.
能够提取那些深度特征
So does it transfer learning, taking features of learning one domain and
他所做的就是转换学习 能够把一个领域中学习到的特征
applies a data set in different domain.
用到另外一个不同领域的数据集中
So this data set here is my image train data.
这边的数据就是我的的 image_traindata
So this is the two commands that you have to do.
这边仅仅用了两条代码
Pretty simple.
很简单
Let me decrease the font size so that it'll be a little bit more visible.
然后减小字体大小 可以看得更清楚一些
The two commands that you have to do to do the transfer learning.
这两条代码用来做转移学习
So take the image net training on the network and
所以我们用网上训练的特征
apply it to this Safari 10 dataset.
运用到Sframe 的数据中
Now computing this deep features takes a few minutes and
计算深度特征仅仅需要几分钟
so I'm not going to do this right now.
我现在就准备做这个
Instead I'm just gonna tell you that our deep mod.
我会告诉你我们的深度模型
If I show you the image_train data.
如果我给你显示iamge_traindata
What I did was, if I just show you the head, the first few lines.
我仅仅给你展示前几行
What you'll see is that we have an image id, we have an image, which
你可以看到我们有着图片ID 图片
we'll looking at, you have the label, and you have a column for deep features.
也就是你看到的 然后就是标签 和一列叫做深度特征
So I precomputed that, and I saved it inside the s frame.
所以说提前运算了 然后储存到SFrame
So it's already saved and precomputed.
现在它已经被保存下了
And it also has another column image_array that has the raw pixels that we used to
它还有最后一列叫做image_array 有着原始像素
train the raw pixel model.
那是我们之前用来做训练原始像素模型的一列
So the deep_features are already in there.
所以说深度特征已经在这了
But if you run those two commands, you'd be computing them yourself on this data
如果你运行这两行代码 你就能够自己在这个数据集中计算深度特征了
set, or in any data set that you want.
或者说在别的数据集中计算
So let's go ahead and
然后让我们继续
now that we have the deep features,
现在我们有了深度特征
let's train a deep model.
让我们来训练深度模型
So, Given the deep features,
有了深度特征
let's train a classifier.
让我们训练分类器
So now, we're gonna train a simple classifier using the deep features.
所以我们会用深度特征训练一个分类器
I'm gonna call this deep_ features_model instead of the raw pixel model.
所以我会叫做深度特征模型 而不再用原始像素模型
And the deep_features_model is also gonna be just calling logistical regression.
所以用.create这个指令 我们以前用过的
So .create and if you remember from lecture, we discussed that you can take
我们用.create这个指令 我们之前用过的
those deep features and plug in a simple classifier at the end in this case, so
我们会用到深度特征 然后并把它用到简单的分类器中
just plug in logistical regression.
仅仅是把它用到逻辑斯蒂模型
So as input, I'm gonna give it the image_train_data.
模型的输入数据是image_train_data
And for features,
我们不再用原始像素
instead of using the raw pixel,
而是特征
I'm going to use the deep_features.
所以会用到deep_features
And finally, I'm gonna tell it that the label, sorry, the target,
最后我会说到标签 噢不 是目标
the thing that I'm trying to predict here, is given by the label column.
也就是我们所要预测的 会在标签这一列中
And there you go.
你去到那里
So now, we're learning a classifier and it's down here,
我们正在训练分类器
using on those 2,000 images only using,
用到2000张图片
using features completed in this deep near network,
用之前训练完的特征
the one in 2012 deep learning competition.
也就是那个2012年比赛中完成的
So now, let's first explore the model, just apply it for some data.
让我们来仔细研究这个模型吧 我们先用它应用到一些数据上
So, I'm going to, we're gonna
我要做的是
Apply the deep features model
先输入标题
to the first few images of test set.
把深度模型用到第一组测试数据中
Just like we did with the raw pixel model, we're gonna apply it in this case.
就像我们之前在原始像素模型中用到的一样  我们也会同样应用
So remember we took the image_test data and we looked at the first three images.
所以记住 我们想要看前三张图
So 0, 1 and 2.
也就是索引为0 1 2的图片
And here's what those images look like.
来看一下这三张图到底是什么?
And I'm gonna type .show and
输入.show来显示
just remind you that we have a cat, a car, and another cat.
提醒一下应该是猫 车 猫
And let's go ahead and just run this to see what we predict.
我们先运行一下预测的结果
So I'm gonna take my deep_feature_model,
会用到deep_feature_model
and I'm going to predict on this three images,
然后预测这三张图
so image_test of 0:3.
输入的数据是image_test[0:3]
And remember cat, car.
记住正确的标签是猫 车 猫
Cat and it says cat, automobile, cat.
他的标签是 猫 机动车 猫
So basically it got those three exactly right.
预测完全正确
Which is exciting.
完美!
So something that sucked really, really did badly using the raw pixels.
原始像素模型真的很糟糕
Now using these deep features as well, on those three points it gets exactly right.
如果用深度学习模型 前三个全对了
But let's actually evaluate the deep model more formally.
那我们来正式的用模型预测
So, we're gonna do next is compute
下一步就是
the test_data accuracy of
计算测试深度学习的准确率
And here we go.
我们去到这里
So how we're gonna do that?
我们该怎么做呢?
We're just gonna do deep_features_model.evaluate
deep_features_model.evaluate这行代码
just like we did with the raw pixel model.
就像我们在原始像素模型中用到的
Here we can do .evaluate.
让我们来衡量结果吧
And as input we're gonna give it the test data.
输入值是测试数据
So image_test.
也就是image_test
And remember the raw pixel model got 46% accuracy.
记住我们原始像素模型有着46%的准确率
It was bad.
有点糟糕
Here by using deep features we now get 78% accuracy, which is quite good.
但是如果用深度学习模型 78%的正确率 很好了
It's close to state of the art.
已经到达预期的目标了
Even if you're learning more data it's quite good compared to the 46%.
如果你去预测更多的数据 相比较46%而言 预测准确率还是很好
So the deep features provide you with a great tool for
所以说深度特征提供了一个
taking just a little bit small piece of data, running for the deep features and
一个仅仅用很小的数据 用来测试深度特征
get quite good accuracy doing image classification task here.
然后能在分类任务中 做到很好的准确率
[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community